Prints and Printing Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Latin America (Box 10)
  - United States (Box 10)
    - 20th Century (Box 10)
      - Weber, Max, 1881- (Box 12)
      - Weir, Julian Alden, 1852-1919 (Box 12)
      - Wells, James L., 1902- (Box 12)
      - Wengenroth, Stow (Box 12)
      - West, Benjamin, 1738-1820 (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 12)
        - Apotheosis of Prince Alfred & Prince Octavius (Box 12)
        - Death of Wolfe (Box 12)
        - King Lear (Box 12)
        - Penn's Treaty (Box 12)
      - Whistler, James A.M., 1834-1903 [Slide boxes 67-68] (Box 12)
      - White, Charles, 1918-1982 [Slide box 68] (Box 12)
      - Woiseri, John L.B. de, ac.1797-1815 (Box 12)
        X Woiseri, John L. Boqueta de
      - Wood, Franklin T., -1945 (Box 12)
      - Wood, Grant, 1892-1942 (Box 12)
      - Woodwille, Richard (after) (Box 12)
      - Worrall, Henry, 1825-1902 (Box 12)
      - Yunkers, Adja, 1900- (Box 12)